

Stephan Benchemoul

Full Stack Web Developer

Phone: +972 (0) 544-522614 **Location:** Tel Aviv, Israel

Website: https://stephanbenchemoul.com/

Email: stephanbazbaz@gmail.com

Full Stack Web Developer. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, PHP OOP, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL, Node js, Strong background in project management and customer relations.

EXPERIENCE

PWM 1.2020 till present

Front end developer

Freelance Front end developer

Recommendations -

Orel Ohayon

tel +972504704047

Inception 3.2020 - 5.2020

QA

QA for Bookful book app

Self Employed 2008 - 2019

Sound Engineer / Music Production

Recording studio sound engineer, music producer

EDUCATION

John Bryce 2019 - 2020

Diploma

Full Stack Web developer

Completed the course with honors

S.A.E Australia 2006-2008

Bachelor degree

Sound Engineering

SKILLS

- *React
- *Redux
- *Material
- *Node JS
- *Angular
- *Python
- *Wordpress
- *SQL
- *Mongo DB

- *Vue
- *Docker
- *Bootstrap